‪SPOOKY IN LOVE
‪EPISODE 3
‪How dare you blackmail me?
‪I didn't make a fuss
‪when you copied my designs last season.
‪But I didn't think you'd copy
‪my ‪haenyeo‪ diver dress.
‪It was a special dress I made
‪while thinking of my grandmother.
‪Hey, listen.
‪Why would I copy the design
‪of a lowly nobody like you?
‪You can run your mouth all you want,
‪but who would believe you?
‪Wait and find out if they believe me.
‪Circumstantial evidence
‪that you copied my designs
‪was caught on the surveillance cameras.
‪You came well-prepared, didn't you?
‪Give me that phone.
‪Put my name on the design.
‪Give me the phone!
‪-Say you used my designs!
‪-Give me the damn phone!
‪Da-mi!
‪Don't you have something to say?
‪What do you mean?
‪It wasn't a coincidence, was it?
‪The mountain where we first met,
‪the taxi driver's body in the trunk,
‪and now, Jang Eun-ju.
‪It's a huge stretch,
‪but let's say that was all a coincidence.
‪But for this to be by chance too?
‪What is it you want to say?
‪If it were you…
‪Let's talk about it another time.
‪You should go inside and warm up.
‪About earlier…
‪Thank you.
‪I might be used to how things are,
‪but that doesn't mean I'm not afraid.
‪Please take care of this for me.
‪You'd be better at handling it than me.
‪I swear, it was a setup.
‪There must be a mistake!
‪-Don't take any photos.
‪-It's all just a misunderstanding!
‪-Don't take photos.
‪-Ms. Kim!
‪-Ms. Jung!
‪-Can you prove it was…
‪-Ms. Kim.
‪-Yes?
‪Find out whoever did this.
‪-I'll demand reparation.
‪-Yes, ma'am.
‪Be gentle with her.
‪Come on out. Watch your step.
‪-Thank you. Please watch your step.
‪-Grandma?
‪This is where you'll be staying.
‪You'll rest in the lobby for a while,
‪and then we'll hand out the keys.
‪We'll show you where to go then.
‪-Shall we?
‪-Hey.
‪Grandma, are you in Jeju Island?
‪Why would I be there? I'm at the temple.
‪-Are you in Jeju Island?
‪-Yeah.
‪Are you sure you're not here?
‪What nonsense are you on about?
‪By the way, you must stay away
‪from large bodies of water today.
‪Okay.
‪Man, is she psychic or something?
‪Did you reach the airport safely?
‪Yeah, I'm almost there.
‪You didn't have to send a car.
‪I heard about the unfortunate accident.
‪I'll let you buy me a meal
‪if you're that grateful.
‪Sure.
‪I'll be going to Seoul soon,
‪so don't forget.
‪Why are you doing that yourself
‪when we have gardeners?
‪I heard about the nuisance.
‪Oh, it's been taken care of.
‪By the way,
‪did you have a visitor earlier?
‪They grow so quickly.
‪If you don't pluck them in time,
‪the weeds will take over the whole garden.
‪Hey.
‪You should stay with her
‪until Da-mi is moved to the burial site.
‪We can't both miss work,
‪so I had to come back.
‪But it just breaks my heart.
‪Okay, bye.
‪I was definitely within arm's reach,
‪but I get the feeling
‪she deliberately avoided grabbing me.
‪About earlier… Thank you.
‪I might be used to how things are,
‪but that doesn't mean I'm not afraid.
‪What was she thanking me for?
‪She's a strange one.
‪I heard you rejected Min-hwan's offer.
‪Yes.
‪I'll flesh out the strategy
‪I showed you last time.
‪Review it for me again.
‪I'm confident I can manage.
‪How did it feel to see him again?
‪Well…
‪Did you send me to Jeju Island
‪because of Min-hwan?
‪Yes, and since we're on the topic…
‪I quite like him. What about you?
‪You mean, romantically?
‪He's just a friend I went to school with.
‪I told you last time, didn't I?
‪To squash the rumor
‪that's going on about you,
‪marriage is the best option.
‪-Grandma.
‪-We can't have such rumors.
‪It's not just about the hotel.
‪What about our family's reputation?
‪Dispel the rumor yourself,
‪with a marriage.
‪Come on, this isn't the Joseon Dynasty.
‪You can't force me to get married.
‪Your marriage
‪isn't just any union.
‪What if the line of succession
‪passes to Dong-jun and Ha-ri?
‪There is the disadvantage
‪that their father isn't my biological son,
‪but you know that
‪when it comes to succession,
‪it's not just about blood.
‪With Min-hwan's help,
‪you could sign with a foreign hotel chain,
‪and naturally get together in the process…
‪I have no intention of doing that.
‪And I
‪don't plan to wait for long.
‪This is the right time
‪to clear up the rumors
‪that are going around about you.
‪Get married within two months.
‪If you don't,
‪I'll bring the Reina licensing talk
‪back to the table.
‪And Siena Hall too.
‪Well, at least
‪make it an engagement for now.
‪Since it was my engagement ceremony
‪that fell through.
‪The deadline remains the same. Two months.
‪On that note, I'd be happy with Min-hwan.
‪But like you said,
‪this isn't the Joseon Dynasty.
‪Still, he should at least
‪measure up to our family.
‪Okay. Let's get back to it.
‪Go on ahead.
‪Now, you're putting Seung-jae behind you
‪and getting out there
‪on blind dates, okay?
‪We bought everything you wanted.
‪Okay.
‪Does Grandma have no interest
‪in opening a department store?
‪Reina Department Store.
‪I'm sure I'd do a good job running it.
‪It's hard enough to get her
‪to give us another art gallery.
‪Forget about a department store.
‪Yeo-ri hasn't caught on yet, right?
‪About the hotel artworks.
‪Cheon Ha-ri?
‪Is that you, Min-hwan?
‪Wow, how long has it been?
‪Oh, my goodness. Look who it is.
‪How have you been?
‪I've been very well.
‪When did you come back to Korea?
‪Well, not too long ago.
‪We haven't met in a while.
‪How about we eat together?
‪I'm here to buy a gift, so I can't today.
‪I'll treat you to something nice soon.
‪You too, Ms. Ok.
‪Come in.
‪Chairwoman Baek.
‪Min-hwan.
‪It's been so long.
‪-This is for you.
‪-Goodness.
‪Oh, gosh.
‪It's beautiful.
‪You didn't have to get me anything.
‪It's so nice to see you in person
‪after just some phone calls.
‪-It really is.
‪-Let's sit down.
‪You haven't changed at all.
‪You look even more radiant.
‪Oh, don't you tease an old woman.
‪I heard you and Yeo-ri
‪didn't reach an agreement.
‪You sent her over knowing
‪how it would turn out.
‪I appreciate the cooperation.
‪Goodness.
‪Should we have dinner with Yeo-ri?
‪I'd love to.
‪What was it that you liked to eat?
‪Anything you like?
‪I don't really mind it much.
‪Hello, ma'am.
‪Ms. Cheon's in, right?
‪She just left to go home.
‪Should I give her a call?
‪No need.
‪She doesn't even take my calls after work.
‪I've spoiled her.
‪That's too bad.
‪We'll have to eat together
‪some other time.
‪No. I like this even better.
‪We can spend some quality time.
‪Right?
‪Let's just relax and eat something nice.
‪Sounds good.
‪Min-hwan and Ji-hwan aren't twins?
‪Keep your voice down.
‪My sister will kill me if she hears you.
‪The truth is, after my sister
‪learned she was infertile,
‪she adopted a baby from the US.
‪But right before she returned to Korea,
‪-she miraculously got pregnant.
‪-Oh, gosh.
‪That's why she delayed her return
‪and came back
‪after giving birth to Ji-hwan.
‪I wondered why she stayed abroad so long.
‪So Min-hwan was adopted, after all.
‪-Exactly.
‪-No wonder…
‪Could that be why they want to
‪send Min-hwan abroad to study?
‪What are you doing over there?
‪Yeo-ri, you're here too.
‪-Join us for some fruit.
‪-No, thank you.
‪We were on our way out.
‪Were you?
‪Let's go.
‪What do you want?
‪We agreed to a bet.
‪Can't it wait?
‪No way. A promise is a promise.
‪Keep your word.
‪If I win,
‪give me the game console
‪you bought yesterday.
‪That's not fair. It's mine.
‪Then beat me.
‪Hey, Gang-uk!
‪-I think I forgot something.
‪-Gang-uk.
‪-What?
‪-I got the office next to yours.
‪Then we're just neighbors.
‪We have a connection, don't we?
‪-Will you please…
‪-Here.
‪Thank you.
‪How long has it been?
‪What do you mean?
‪We met at Do-jun's wedding.
‪That's a really long time for us.
‪-Jeez, you still yap too much.
‪-Isn't that Prosecutor Im Seo-hyeon
‪from the Ministry of Justice's
‪Criminal Affairs Division?
‪What's going on? Do they know each other?
‪They don't just know each other.
‪What do you mean? Did they date?
‪I wouldn't say they dated.
‪Ever since
‪they went to the same university,
‪their relationship has been like
‪that of the Earth and the moon.
‪The Earth and the moon?
‪-Earth's gravity pulls the moon, right?
‪-Right.
‪Im pulls Ma close with all her might,
‪but Ma spins around her
‪without ever getting too close.
‪It's quite strange.
‪Whenever Ma is
‪transferred somewhere for work,
‪Im also gets herself transferred there.
‪And when Ma transfers somewhere else,
‪Im follows him there too.
‪Does she have connections
‪with the higher-ups?
‪That's what I don't get.
‪It's fascinating.
‪The Earth and the moon…
‪Yes?
‪Hello.
‪It's Mr. Kang, the CEO.
‪-Welcome.
‪-Thank you.
‪I didn't expect to get a call from you.
‪I felt bad that we didn't get to talk
‪after meeting at the department store.
‪It's been so long since we met,
‪and I wanted to treat you to a meal.
‪Was the drive here all right?
‪-Yes, it was fine.
‪-Was it?
‪The thing is, I heard somewhere
‪that G1A Group is trying to sell
‪Fiel Seoul to another company.
‪CL Group has decided to join
‪the bidding war to acquire it, right?
‪Well, we haven't
‪made our position official yet.
‪Your sources are pretty quick.
‪They say some things are open secrets,
‪but to be honest,
‪those in the business know everything.
‪Anyway, I heard you spearheaded
‪the Fiel Seoul acquisition.
‪Well, yes.
‪If you manage to buy Fiel Seoul,
‪will that cement your position
‪as the successor?
‪I'm so impressed, Mr. Kang.
‪So why did you want to see me today?
‪Oh, well…
‪From what I heard,
‪you'll need a great sum of money
‪to win the bid.
‪Do you have the necessary funds?
‪I'm aware that they have a massive debt.
‪If you happen to be
‪in need of more funds,
‪our Reina Resort could offer
‪a partial investment in your project.
‪I appreciate it,
‪but we have our own financial company.
‪Not to mention that this acquisition
‪was my father's long-held ambition,
‪so I have his full support.
‪Oh, yes. I'm sure you do.
‪Right, Chairman Kang
‪and his long-held ambition.
‪Let's work together
‪on another project some other time.
‪Sure.
‪Yes, I would love that.
‪Gosh, my silly daughter Ha-ri.
‪She never stopped talking about you,
‪but I can't reach her today
‪and I don't know where she went.
‪Hey, Ha-ri.
‪Take a seat.
‪This is the last time I'm visiting
‪out of loyalty as your ex.
‪Ha-ri, I think
‪I'll be out of here pretty soon.
‪That's impossible.
‪You can't get out
‪when they found her body.
‪It's just not official yet.
‪Let's patch things up when I get out.
‪Patch what up?
‪You ruined our company's
‪entire reputation.
‪Ha-ri, nothing's easier to manipulate
‪than public opinion.
‪My dad's already working on it.
‪That woman was a gold-digger
‪with a dirty past.
‪She used me from start to finish.
‪I believe you.
‪But my mom's turned her back on you.
‪The engagement's off,
‪and I'm supposed to cut you off.
‪Ha-ri.
‪The heart follows where the money is.
‪My dad's still going strong.
‪He has all the power I need.
‪As soon as I get out,
‪I swear on my life
‪that I'll help you take over Reina.
‪Why? What do you want?
‪I just can't seem to make sense of it.
‪How did you know where to go?
‪You just happened to be there
‪and found a body in the water tank,
‪and the prosecutor showed up too?
‪About the weird rumors
‪going around about you…
‪Do you still see ghosts or something?
‪You do, don't you?
‪You always go
‪a bit too far.
‪I can't let a possessed shaman
‪take over Reina.
‪If I reveal the truth about that,
‪Grandma will give up the idea
‪of letting you take over.
‪If that's all you have to say,
‪I'm leaving.
‪You that inhabit the body of this woman!
‪You evil spirit!
‪Begone!
‪Yeo-ri?
‪Yeo-ri.
‪Grandma.
‪Well done.
‪You held up well.
‪Shaman Baek said he suppressed the evil.
‪How do you feel?
‪Do you still see things?
‪I don't…
‪anymore.
‪I guess they're gone.
‪Do it again.
‪-Again?
‪-Do it again.
‪A hotel is not a facility!
‪-It's where memories are made.
‪-Let's go, Reina!
‪-Let's go!
‪-Enjoy yourselves, everyone.
‪-Let's drink.
‪You want me to step down
‪when I indicted him?
‪That makes no sense.
‪Didn't I tell you to give in
‪when you had the chance?
‪Even so. You should've shielded me.
‪Don't you know how we work?
‪We do whatever the higher-ups tell us.
‪What if I were to get caught
‪in the backlash?
‪I must survive if I'm to help you out.
‪I have to say, Assemblyman Park
‪has still got some fight left in him.
‪Even after what his son did,
‪he managed to fight back hard.
‪TRANSFER NOTICE
‪CRIMINAL PROSECUTION 12, MA GANG-UK
‪PROSECUTOR MA GANG-UK TO COLD CASE UNIT
‪We had already decided to beef up
‪Criminal Prosecution
‪and revamp the Cold Case Unit anyway.
‪Solve some cases while you're over there.
‪I'll bring you back
‪when the time is right.
‪Don't you think things are going backward?
‪Why am I getting demoted
‪for solving a case?
‪Accept it and go with the flow.
‪It's not like this is anything new.
‪Fine. You wait and see.
‪Let's see what you say
‪if this happens to you.
‪Just go, "Oh, I guess this is it then."
‪"This is just how things are."
‪If you take everything to heart,
‪you'll end up dying young.
‪-Aren't I right?
‪-You are.
‪I'm not even surprised, you know.
‪Why are you more immature
‪than your junior?
‪Why do you keep yawning?
‪Did you not sleep well?
‪It's not that.
‪I just had a really stressful dream
‪that felt so real.
‪In the dream,
‪I was going somewhere when something
‪suddenly appeared in front of me.
‪It was my late grandmother.
‪-Okay.
‪-I asked her what was up.
‪She just stared at me,
‪then all of a sudden
‪she went and…
‪She hit me. She actually punched me.
‪"You good-for-nothing brat,
‪how dare you not visit me once
‪while I was alive?"
‪"You don't deserve a good night's sleep!"
‪She was exactly how I remember her.
‪You know those old canes
‪that old people used?
‪It hurt when she hit you, didn't it?
‪Don't even ask. It hurt badly.
‪Who are you?
‪That wasn't a dream.
‪Ms. Cheon?
‪Cheon Yeo-ri.
‪It's Cheon Yeo-ri, the heiress.
‪Mr. Ma.
‪It's Prosecutor Ma Gang-uk.
‪We shared a bed.
‪You can't say that.
‪-People could get the wrong idea.
‪-What?
‪What brings you here? Where are the rest?
‪I didn't bring anyone else.
‪I'm here on my own.
‪I didn't think you'd step foot
‪in places like this.
‪They must know each other well.
‪They don't just know each other.
‪I think they're best friends.
‪We can't stand not getting answers.
‪-Right.
‪-Hello. How are you?
‪-Shall we?
‪-It's a pleasure to meet you.
‪Stop.
‪Maintain your distance.
‪Take three steps back.
‪Okay. Three steps back.
‪One, two, three.
‪-Sit down.
‪-Okay.
‪I'm doing this for your sake, you know.
‪I'm putting up a wall to keep you safe.
‪If you make the mistake
‪of sitting with me,
‪terrible things could happen to you.
‪That's why I paid in advance
‪to keep the tables around me empty.
‪So no one can even come near me.
‪I get that you want to flaunt your money,
‪but why bother to come here
‪just to drink alone?
‪"Why bother"?
‪It's not the same.
‪Here, if I look up from a drink,
‪I see people.
‪At home, if I look up from a drink…
‪Forget it.
‪-She emptied seven bottles of soju.
‪-She's out of it.
‪Every now and then, I want to drink
‪among some ordinary people.
‪Wait…
‪Do it properly then.
‪-What?
‪-Come and join us.
‪-Yes, sure.
‪-Shall we?
‪No, you can't.
‪-Go away. Leave.
‪-Excuse us.
‪If you join me,
‪you might get a taste of the afterlife.
‪If we do, then so be it.
‪Here.
‪Drink up.
‪You filled my glass, so I should empty it.
‪It's been so long
‪since someone poured me a drink.
‪-They must have a thing.
‪-They're playing hard to get.
‪It's not like that.
‪It's not.
‪Earlier, when I was talking about
‪the dream of my grandma,
‪what did you mean it wasn't a dream?
‪Oh, that?
‪You guys have no idea
‪that the dead come visit you
‪while you sleep, do you?
‪They come and watch you while you sleep.
‪They just stare…
‪like this.
‪They sometimes give you sleep paralysis
‪or even strangle you.
‪People think they're just nightmares.
‪You think they're all dreams, don't you?
‪You would never know
‪when you only ever see one side of things.
‪You can't drink soju out of a bowl.
‪That will kill you.
‪What? Why would I die?
‪No, I mean if you drink this much at once,
‪it'll ruin your liver and your stomach.
‪What if you were to fall ill?
‪It'd be hard on you,
‪but also on your family.
‪Shut up.
‪You think my family would worry about me?
‪What makes you say that?
‪Do you even know me?
‪What do you even know about me
‪to say something like that?
‪What do people like you know
‪when you're able to drink in a crowd?
‪All you see with your two eyes
‪is the outer skin.
‪Skin.
‪This is a skin too.
‪I don't need extra layers like these.
‪Why'd you take off the gloves
‪you're always wearing?
‪-In this pork skin diner…
‪-What?
‪Eating these pork skin…
‪Only seeing the skin that meets the eye…
‪-Wait…
‪-You're just a skin-deep prosecutor!
‪Skin-deep!
‪What the…
‪You should…
‪be stripped…
‪of your skin!
‪Pil-dong.
‪Can you lend me a shirt?
‪I think you'll have to go home like that.
‪What is this?
‪Man, never have I seen
‪such a drunken habit.
‪I mean, forget that she was drunk,
‪but calling me "skin-deep"?
‪And why should I know her?
‪I could say the same about her.
‪Besides, why not drink on her own at home
‪instead of reserving half the diner?
‪She calls herself the CEO of a hotel,
‪yet she pulls
‪a drunken stunt like that in public?
‪Man, it was a new shirt too.
‪Can't you at least react
‪at the bare minimum?
‪Hello?
‪Did you say something?
‪Oh, come on.
‪I'm sick of you. Get out.
‪You can't corner me like this
‪just because we're carpooling in your car.
‪I'm not cornering you.
‪We're here, so get out.
‪Oh, when did we get here?
‪Hello? You go ahead.
‪It's me, Cheon Yeo-ri.
‪What do you want?
‪Well, I think…
‪I might have acted out of line last night.
‪You mean ripping my shirt up?
‪Don't worry about it.
‪It's fine. I threw it away.
‪I'm not fine with what I did.
‪I can't stand owing anyone anything.
‪What did you send me?
‪Yes, I knew it.
‪It's Éthria.
‪Look at this. It's pure silk.
‪How much do these cost?
‪This is a high-end luxury brand,
‪so at least three million won?
‪What?
‪What's the nicest thing Ma can buy
‪without feeling guilty or tethered?
‪Pork belly.
‪What's the nicest thing he can accept?
‪Two cups of iced coffee?
‪That won't do. In that case,
‪I'll carry it very safely…
‪-Why would you take it?
‪-I should.
‪Silk shirts look better on me.
‪-You can't handle them.
‪-That's what you think.
‪You really can't handle a silk shirt.
‪-You don't know--
‪-Éthria goods are…
‪What? Mr. Ma.
‪That Éthria shirt…
‪Hello, good morning.
‪I'm here to see Ms. Cheon.
‪-Oh, Ms. Cheon?
‪-Yes.
‪-Please give me a moment.
‪-Sure.
‪-Hello.
‪-Yes, hi.
‪The hotel gym and sauna, right?
‪I'm Ms. Cheon's executive secretary.
‪Ms. Cheon isn't in at the moment.
‪She sent this to me today.
‪If you're her secretary,
‪pass it to her for me.
‪-No, I can't do that.
‪-Why not?
‪If Ms. Cheon sent it to you herself,
‪we're not allowed to
‪take it back on her behalf.
‪What else am I supposed to do with it?
‪Could you return it yourself,
‪if you don't mind?
‪Jeez…
‪Ms. Eom?
‪Wasn't the man who came to see
‪Ms. Cheon here before?
‪He was. This was his second visit.
‪Could he be a stalker following Ms. Cheon?
‪No, he's a Seoul
‪Central District prosecutor.
‪Could he be pretending to be a prosecutor?
‪I doubt that.
‪His office once sent a questionnaire
‪to our legal team.
‪Oh, right.
‪Do you know why
‪he wanted to see Ms. Cheon?
‪It seems that Ms. Cheon sent him a gift
‪and he wanted to return it.
‪That's a problem.
‪Whether it be from an official
‪or a private standpoint,
‪it's a problem if she sent a gift
‪to a Central District prosecutor.
‪Shouldn't we call a meeting
‪for damage control and countermeasures?
‪If there is a problem,
‪I'm sure Ms. Cheon will handle it.
‪No, no.
‪We need to take action. My hunch says so.
‪It's never wrong.
‪Yes.
‪That's my coffee.
‪Oh, I was wrong.
‪Wrong.
‪It's not that big a favor.
‪Why couldn't she just return it for me?
‪Jeez.
‪Why does she live so far away?
‪No wonder she reserved half the diner.
‪Where did they go?
‪They're the only thing that's missing.
‪Where did I take them off?
‪Who could that be?
‪I didn't order any delivery.
‪It's him again.
‪What's he doing here?
‪How did you find me?
‪I put your address in my GPS.
‪The GPS?
‪How did you get my address?
‪Don't you remember?
‪You gave it to me.
‪I did?
‪I wouldn't…
‪Hey.
‪Hello? Your address.
‪Tell me your address.
‪My address?
‪-My address is Seongbuk-gu, Seoul…
‪-What?
‪Okay.
‪Can you put this into the GPS?
‪I'm really sorry.
‪I was in the middle of something…
‪Never mind that.
‪I just came here to return this.
‪I'm not able to come out right now.
‪Could you leave it by the gate?
‪Sure. I'll do that.
‪I'll leave these here as well.
‪You left them at the diner.
‪What?
‪Why does he have my gloves?
‪I don't need extra layers like these.
‪You should be stripped
‪of your skin!
‪Hey, you forgot your gloves.
‪Oh, no.
‪I must've been out of my mind.
‪I'll leave both of these together
‪-by the gate here.
‪-I did that without my gloves?
‪That's why I couldn't find them anywhere.
‪-What now?
‪-I've left them here.
‪I'm leaving now.
‪Should I ask?
‪Wait. Wait.
‪What?
‪What? Does she want me to come in?
‪Your house is really quiet.
‪Yes.
‪Look, Mr. Ma.
‪By any chance, every now and then,
‪do you happen to see things
‪you weren't able to before?
‪There's a tent in your living room.
‪Yes, well…
‪It's pretty cozy inside.
‪As you can see,
‪this house is too big for me alone.
‪It really is quite big.
‪My parents used to live with me,
‪though not anymore.
‪-Try the tea.
‪-Thanks.
‪Why did you want me to come in?
‪You don't seem the type to have guests.
‪Well, you came all this way,
‪so it felt wrong
‪to just send you on your way.
‪And I wanted to check something too.
‪Check what? With me?
‪So last night…
‪I was a bit out of line.
‪I touched you without my gloves…
‪Who's that kid?
‪Who is that?
‪-He's from next door.
‪-What's he doing here?
‪Playing hide and seek.
‪He comes here sometimes to play.
‪Oh, really?
‪He must be bored.
‪If it's because his parents aren't home,
‪-I'll play with him for a bit.
‪-No.
‪You can't do that.
‪You can't do anything.
‪I'm really good with kids.
‪You were here to return these, right?
‪You returned them and I received them.
‪All is well.
‪You can leave now.
‪Go on your way.
‪Goodbye.
‪-What was that?
‪-The wind.
‪The doors are closed.
‪It couldn't have been the wind.
‪Could it be a burglar?
‪What?
‪They could've scaled the wall
‪to hide somewhere.
‪I worked on a case like that.
‪Listen. I have a security system,
‪so that would be impossible.
‪Wait.
‪I could just be paranoid,
‪but it doesn't hurt to check,
‪and it won't take that long.
‪No.
‪It's not a burglar.
‪It must've been the kid.
‪You see, there's an open door in the back.
‪There is?
‪Goodness, what a sneaky kid.
‪Wait. Mr. Ma.
‪It's fine. It won't take long.
‪-I told you to go.
‪-Just wait.
‪Are you in here?
‪What?
‪You're not in here.
‪I'd better get going then.
‪Ms. Cheon, you'll come with me, right?
‪Where?
‪-Come here.
‪-What are you…
‪What are you doing?
‪How did you know this was a door?
‪What are you…
‪That must be him coming out.
‪Who do you mean?
‪Did you see that?
‪He moved so fast.
‪Gosh, it was like… He almost…
‪That was…
‪Excuse me.
‪Yes?
‪I'm really tired.
‪Please leave.
‪I was too dull-witted to catch on.
‪I'm sorry.
‪My coat.
‪What should I do now?
‪What do I do now?
‪Will he be okay?
‪What should I do?
‪What are you doing over there, kid?
‪Shouldn't you be going home?
‪Library hours are over now.
‪I can't go home.
‪That hurt.
‪I must be
‪way too on edge.
‪Why the hell won't this open?
‪-Hello?
‪He's in my home right now.
‪-Who?
‪-The kid who was playing hide and seek.
‪-The little boy?
‪-Yes.
‪He came all the way to my home.
‪Mr. Ma?
‪I'm here.
‪Over here.
‪Were you out here this whole time?
‪Sit down here with me.
‪What…
‪Who is that kid? He climbs walls too.
‪SOJU
‪You carry this stuff around with you?
‪It's a bag I keep handy
‪in case of emergencies.
‪Try to calm down.
‪Drink that first.
‪Do you feel a bit relaxed now?
‪What do you mean "relaxed"?
‪Are you going to say something
‪that'll shock me?
‪I have what it takes.
‪You can say whatever it is.
‪Go on.
‪Are you sure?
‪No way.
‪You weren't relaxed enough.
‪Here. You need to stay with me.
‪Have a few more sips of alcohol.
‪Gulp it down. Don't spit it out.
‪-He's not here.
‪-Okay.
‪How did you know the body was there?
‪-I was told.
‪-By whom?
‪By a ghost.
‪So she was telling the truth.
‪Should I just turn the lights on?
‪He doesn't like bright lights.
‪You're sticking too close to me.
‪I'm not standing that close.
‪Wait outside if you're scared.
‪I'm not scared, I'm just nervous.
‪-Do you live alone too?
‪-Yes.
‪Your place feels comfortable and cozy.
‪I owe that to my grandma.
‪She sweeps and cleans whenever she visits.
‪Huh? Wait…
‪Does the kid like cars?
‪He's a kid, so he'll be hiding.
‪You must be good with housework.
‪Yes. I'm good at everything I do.
‪Oh, this is just…
‪I always check out of habit.
‪It's a work-related habit.
‪Do you think he could've left?
‪That's strange.
‪Kids rarely leave
‪once they latch onto you.
‪Where do they stay if they don't go?
‪Why? What is it?
‪Kids tend to…
‪Yes?
‪Piggyback on people.
‪Get off me!
‪-Mr. Ma! Keep still!
‪-Get off me!
‪Go away!
‪You said you weren't scared!
‪No! No!
‪Go away!
‪He's off your back now!
‪He's gone!
‪He's gone?
‪SPOOKY IN LOVE
‪What do we do now?
‪More ghosts will come for you.
‪What happened to the other people
‪you came in contact with?
‪The ghosts that visit you early on
‪will be the nasty ones
‪that harass and torment others.
‪You believe in all this?
‪-There must be something about ghosts.
‪-Look.
‪Look at him stuffing his face
‪with all that garlic.
‪What's gotten into him?
‪You swore on your life
‪that you'd help me take over Reina
‪once you get out of here.
‪Did you mean that?
‪You bet I did.
‪It makes no sense that a murderer like him
‪is getting released!
‪Park Seung-jae.
‪I plan to find a weakness
‪instead of going after you,
‪Cheon Yeo-ri.
‪Subtitle translation by: Jennifer Jean Lim